marketing.ai 2015-06-07

# Marketing.AI Privacy Policy

Effective Date: 01 November, 2012

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") explains the privacy practices of Marketing.AI a product of Experts.AI Software Corp., a Vancouver-based company ("Experts.AI", "we", "us" or "our") that apply to (i) the access and use of the www.Marketing.ai website, and any related sub-domains, which are operated by Experts.AI (the "Website"), and (iii) the provision by Experts.AI of services through the Website (the "Services").

EXPERTS.AI IS COMMITTED TO MAINTAINING YOUR PRIVACY PLEASE READ ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SO THAT YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT TYPE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE COLLECT IT, HOW WE USE IT AND TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE IT.

This privacy policy discloses the privacy policy of Experts.AI Software Corp. in relation to the Marketing.AI Website. Your access to the Marketing.AI Website is subject to the [Terms of Service](http://www.marketing.ai/terms-of-service.html) governing Marketing.AI. This privacy policy describes how the Marketing.AI Website collects, uses and shares information about you that it obtains in connection with providing the Marketing.AI Website to you on a subscription basis. Experts.AI collects information from you in the following ways in connection with your use of the Marketing.AI website: (1) information you give to us as part of the sign-up process, and which you may update to us from time to time within your account information, and (2) information automatically collected when you visit any of the Marketing.AI Websites. 

We will only share your information with third parties in accordance with your instructions or as necessary to provide you with a specific service or otherwise in accordance with applicable privacy legislation. As a general rule, we do not and will not sell, rent, share or disclose your personal information without first receiving your permission or as permitted in this Privacy Policy.

When you sign up for the Marketing.AI Website, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself such as your name, email address, billing address, and company name or affiliation. You can view all of the information collected during the registration process by visiting the registration page. You may modify or remove any of your personal information at any time by logging into your account and accessing features that will allow you to edit your profile and account Information. 

After you provide such information and set up your account, we may ask you to provide additional information about yourself on an optional basis. We may ask you for certain financial information, including credit card account data or other payment method data, to process payments for some of our services. Experts.AI may collect any communication it has with you via any means, including e-mail, telephone, and letters. 

By choosing to provide any information to us, you are giving Experts.AI permission to use and store such information consistent with this privacy policy. In addition, Experts.AI automatically collects information about your interactions with the Marketing.AI Website. For example, Experts.AI may log information from your computer and browser, such as your IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, browser type, software and hardware attributes, pages you request, and cookie information. By using the Marketing.AI Services, you are giving Marketing.AI permission to use and store such information consistent with this privacy policy. You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.

Experts.AI may use services that collect data remotely by using “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “clear GIFs,” or similar technologies. Such technologies can recognize certain types of information on your web browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed them and the IP address of the computer from which you viewed them. The Marketing.AI may be linked to or provided through third party websites. Experts.AI is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on such third party websites. When linking or accessing such websites, you should carefully review the privacy policy of such third party to determine how it handles information it separately collects from you. 

Experts.AI uses the information it collects from you to deliver the Marketing.AI to you and continuously enhance your user experience. Generally speaking, we use the collected information to communicate with you, fulfill your requests, customize the content, improve our products and services, protect our and your rights, and comply with laws and regulations. 

We may use your personal information to send you promotional information and updates regarding Marketing.AI and its products and services. You may choose not to receive such information and opt-out of such future communications. All such communications sent to you will also contain instructions for opting-out. The information that we collect from you may be used in aggregate form in various ways to optimize and improve the Marketing.AI Website. While such information may be based on information about you, it will not identify you personally. 

If Experts.AI sells all or part of its business, or makes a sale or transfer of assets, or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, Experts.AI may transfer your personal information and non-personal information to one or more third parties as part of such transaction. You have the choice about whether to disclose your personal information or other information about yourself to Experts.AI. Regardless of your choices with respect to promotional communications and updates regarding content, Experts.AI may send you administrative messages, service announcements, terms and conditions of your account, or other similar communications, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

From time to time, Experts.AI may partner with other companies to jointly offer products or services. If you purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly-offered product or service from Experts.AI, Experts.AI may share your information collected in connection with your purchase or expression of interest with our joint promotion partner(s). Experts.AI does not control our business partners’ use of the information, and their use of the information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may opt not to purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly offered product or service. 

We may disclose your information if required to by law enforcement officials or governmental agencies (i) when required by law; or (ii) to establish our compliance with applicable laws, rules, regulations, or guidelines. Experts.AI takes security of information seriously. We host both our North American and Rest of World systems with Amazon Web Services that has robust security protocols and has obtained ISO 27001 certification. For more information about Amazon Web Services security, visit <http://aws.amazon.com/security/>.

From time to time, we may make changes to this privacy policy. In order to ensure that you are familiar with our most updated policies and practices, you should check the effective date indicated above of this privacy policy each time you use the Marketing.AI Website. If we make any changes, we will notify you of such changes by posting the updated privacy policy on the Marketing.AI Website. We may also send you an email alerting you of such changes. You will be bound by any such changes to the policy when you use the Marketing.AI Website after those changes have been posted. If we make material revisions concern practices where we have represented that we will obtain your consent to use or disclose your personal information, we will obtain your consent before taking any action inconsistent with those representations. 

Contacting Experts.AI Software Corp.  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Marketing.AI Website, or your dealings with Experts.AI, please contact us at: support@experts.ai or by mail at:  
Experts.AI Software Corp.  
422 Richards Street, #170  
Vancouver, BC V6B 2Z4
